accountnow.com 2009-02-07

# AccountNow Privacy Policy- Company Info|AccountNow Prepaid Card

IMPORTANT - PLEASE READ CAREFULLY

PRIVACY DISCLOSURE

We recognize the importance you place on your privacy and the confidentiality of your financial information. We think it is important for you to be informed of the policies we have in place to safeguard your privacy. 

And rest assured, AccountNow will never rent or sell your information to anyone without your explicit permission. Period! 

This Privacy Disclosure explains the privacy policies of Palm Desert National Bank ("PDNB") or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) and AccountNow with respect to the AccountNow Prepaid MasterCard or AccountNow Prepaid Visa Card program.

A. DEFINITIONS

**1\. Affiliate**

An affiliate is defined as one or more of the following: 

  * A company PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) or AccountNow owns or controls;
  * A company that owns or controls PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) or AccountNow; or
  * A company that is owned or controlled by the same company that owns or controls PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) or AccountNow.

Ownership does not mean complete ownership, but refers to enough ownership to control the company. 

**2\. Cookies**

Piece of information delivered from a Web site to the client's browser, and then stored on the hard drive. Examples are login or registration information, online “shopping cart” information, user preferences, etc. Cookies can be read by that Web site on the next visit. 

**3\. Nonaffiliated Third Party** A nonaffiliated third party is defined as one of the following: 

  * A person who is not employed by PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) or AccountNow; or 
  * A company that is not an affiliate of PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) or AccountNow.

These nonaffiliated third parties may include financial services providers, such as mortgage and insurance companies; nonfinancial companies, such as direct marketers, retailers and publishers; and others, such as nonprofit organizations. 

**4\. Opt out**

To Opt out means a choice you can make to prevent certain sharing or use of information. We will explain how you can exercise this choice. 

**5\. Personally Identifiable Information**

Personally identifiable information is that information about you that is personal to you, and can include your name, address, social security number, telephone number, and date of birth. 

**6\. SSL (Secure Socket Layer)**

An SSL creates a secure connection between AccountNow and your computer. Information sent through an SSL is turned into and sent as an encoded message, which is decoded by the receiver. This prevents anyone from using the information if intercepted during transmission. 

**7\. We, Us, and Our**

We, Us, and our, refers to PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) and AccountNow. AccountNow is the marketer and PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank) is the bank that is working with us on those programs. 

**8\. You and your**

You and your, refers to customers with an AccountNow product or service issued by PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank), as well as any consumers who apply for an product or service issued by PDNB or MetaBank (see back of card for your issuing bank). 

B. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND DISCLOSE

**1\. What Kind of Information Do We Collect?**

To provide you with the best service, it is important that we collect and maintain accurate personal information about you. Some of the personal information we collect may be nonpublic. This means the information cannot be found on public sources, such as telephone directories or government records. For example: 

  * We may obtain information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, social security number, and date of birth.
  * We may obtain information such as your tax identification number, credit worthiness and credit history. 
  * We may obtain information about your transactions with us, or others, such as account balance, payment history, parties to transactions and card use. 
  * We may obtain information such as your Internet service provider (ISP), your computer's operating system and Web browser, your Web site use and your product and service preferences from your visits to our Web site. This information is not usually personally identifiable. 
  * Information from a consumer reporting agency, such as verification of your identity.
  * Any other information you may provide to us. For instance, you may provide information via forms.

C. HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

**1\. How Do We Collect Your Information?**

We collect information about you from applications and other forms you submit to us, from your dealings with us and others, from our Web site and from other sources, such as government and consumer reporting agencies. 

**2\. How Do We Collect Information Through Our Web Site?**

We can collect information about how people use our Web site by tracking the sites that lead people to our Web site or the number of views our Web pages receive; this is not personally identifiable information. 

We may obtain identifiable information through our Web site by using “Cookies.” Cookies are used to tailor the website in order to improve the customer experience of those visiting our site more than once. 

D. HOW INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED

**1\. Do We Share Your Information?**

We will never rent or sell your information to anyone without your explicit permission; however, there are instances in which your information may be shared with other companies. 

We may share information we collect about you with other companies (including Affiliates and Non Affiliates Third Party) in order to provide services on either our behalf or yours. For example, this includes companies that perform marketing services for us as well as companies who assist us in preparing and mailing statements and responding to customer inquiries. Other information shared may also include financial service providers, such as insurance companies 

**2\. What Information is Shared?**

All information that is directly or indirectly collected from you may be shared. 

**3\. Can You Stop Your Information From Being Shared?**

If you prefer us not to share your information with other companies, you may “Opt out” by contacting us via U.S. mail or telephone to inform us on your decision. We will honor any request to stop sharing your information unless it is permitted or required by law. 

**4\. How Do You Contact Us?**

If you have any questions or requests, you can contact customer service at 1-866-925-2036 from 5:00 AM to 6:00PM PST, Monday through Friday. You can also contact us by U.S. mail at: 

AccountNow Customer Service  
PO Box 1967   
San Ramon, CA 94583  

E. HOW INFORMATION IS SAFEGUARDED

**1\. How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and applicable state standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. Customer information is safely stored in a secure data center. Also, an SSL connection is used to share information between us and your computer. 

**2\. How Do We Protect the Confidentiality of Your Information?**

Your information is only accessible for business purposes to authorized employees which are properly trained to handle such sensitive information. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information about you to our employees who have a need to know such information (e.g., to process your transactions). We train our employees on the importance of customer privacy and confidentiality. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard the nonpublic personal information of our customers. Employees who violate the privacy policies of AccountNow will be subject to disciplinary action and possibly termination. 

F. ADDITIONAL POLICY INFORMATION

**1\. What If You Are a Former Customer?**

The policies and practices discussed in this Privacy Disclosure also apply to former customers. 

**2\. What If You Click a Link on Our Web site?**

Our Web site may feature links to other sites offering goods, services or information. Be aware that the content on other sites are not apart of AccountNow, unless otherwise indicated. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any Web site before providing any personal information. 

**3\. How Do You Access Your Information?**

You can access most of the information we have about you online at www.accountnow.com or www.accountnowvisa.com (depending on the card you have). 

**4\. How Do You Correct Your Information?**

If you notice an error or need to update the information we have about you, contact us via U.S. mail or telephone to make the appropriate changes. 

**5\. Can The Privacy Disclosure Change?**

As we try to provide you with better service, we may change our Privacy Disclosure from time to time. If you are a current customer, you will be notified if any changes are made and a revised disclosure will be sent to you describing any new practices as required by law. 

**6\. California Residents**

Your state law requires us to obtain your consent before sharing information about you with others. We will not share information we collect about you with affiliates and non-affiliated third parties, unless otherwise permitted by law. 

**7\. Vermont Residents**

Your state law requires us to obtain your consent before sharing information about you with others. We will not share information we collect about you with affiliates and non-affiliated third parties, unless otherwise permitted by law. 

"" 

****-

Instant Approval, Guaranteed*

No ChexSystems / Credit Check

AccountNow Prepaid Visa card is issued by MetaBank pursuant to a license by Visa U.S.A. Inc. AccountNow Prepaid MasterCard card and AccountNow Money Share Prepaid Maestro Card are issued by MetaBank pursuant to license by MasterCard International Incorporated. Funds are insured up to $250,000 by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC). MasterCard and the MasterCard Brand Mark are registered trademarks of MasterCard International Incorporated. If you sign up for Credit Builder, your bill pay transactions will be reported to PRBC®. 

†iAdvance is an open-end line of credit offered by MetaBank, a federally chartered savings association, located in Sioux Falls, S.D. Certain fees and eligibility requirements apply. Consult the iAdvance Terms and Conditions for further details. 

*The USA PATRIOT Act is a Federal law that requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify, and record information that identifies each person who opens an account. You will be asked to provide your name, address, date of birth, and other information that will allow us to identify you. You may also be asked to provide documentation as proof of identification. Guaranteed Approval is contingent upon successfully passing this mandatory identification confirmation. Cardholders must complete a separate application for iAdvance Line of Credit. Certain fees and eligibility requirements apply.

**Conditions and exceptions apply. Visa’s Zero Liability policy covers U.S.–issued cards only and does not apply to ATM transactions, PIN transactions not processed by Visa, or certain commercial card transactions. Cardholder must notify issuer promptly of any unauthorized use. Consult issuer for additional details or visit www.visa.com/security. 

AccountNow reserves the right to modify or discontinue any product, services or special offers with or without prior notice.

AccountNow is a trademark of AccountNow, Inc.  
All other trademarks, service marks and other registered marks are the property of their respective owners.

© Copyright 2008 AccountNow, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
